(Sheldon:)For all we know,
there are hidden compartments
(Sheldon:)lousy with Jane Fonda
workout videos.
(Leonard:)If there was
a hidden compartment,
(Leonard:)don't you think you'd be
stuffed in it by now?
(Sheldon:)Are we all up to date on our
yellow fever inoculations?
(Howard:)You don't need a yellow fever
shot to go to Mexico.
(Sheldon:)You can never be too careful.
(Sheldon:)I got one last year
before I went to Epcot.
(Amy:)So, Penny,
how's married life?
(Penny:)Oh, it's good.
(Penny:)I just wish Leonard
would work up the courage
(Penny:)to tell Sheldon
he's moving in here.
(Bernadette:)You guys still aren't
living together?
(Penny:)We are. I mean, he sleeps here.
(Penny:)But it's only a matter of time
(Penny:)before Sheldon has a bad dream
(Penny:)and tries to climb into bed
(Penny:)with the Leonard-shaped
pile of pillows.
(Bernadette:)Speaking of Sheldon,
(Bernadette:)how's single life treating you?
(Amy:)Fine, I guess.
(Amy:)I've been focusing on me.
(Amy:)I was thinking about
changing my wardrobe.
Yes!
Good for you!
(Amy:)But then I decided I don't want
to go changing who I am
(Amy:)just because of some man.
(Penny:)Yes.
Good for you.